{
    "subject": "resource/Vesta_M._Roy",
    "predicate": "property/placeOfBirth",
    "object": "resource/Dearborn,_Michigan",
    "human_readable": "Vesta M. Roy was born in Dearborn, Michigan.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9375348687171936,
            "question": "Where was Vesta M. Roy born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9303563237190247,
            "question": "Were there any notable events happening in Dearborn when Vesta M. Roy was born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9032045602798462,
            "question": "What state was Vesta M. Roy born in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8213340044021606,
            "question": "What year was Vesta M. Roy born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7930026650428772,
            "question": "What could have influenced Vesta M. Roy's life growing up in Dearborn?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5935306549072266,
            "question": "What might Vesta M. Roy be known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5751147270202637,
            "question": "Is there any information available about Vesta M. Roy's family?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5716821551322937,
            "question": "Do you know anything about Dearborn, Michigan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5240682363510132,
            "question": "Is there any information available about people who were also born in Dearborn?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4627037048339844,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Vesta M. Roy?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Vesta M. Roy was born in Dearborn, Michigan.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3281_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any information available about people who were also born in Dearborn?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3281_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Do you know anything about Dearborn, Michigan?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3281_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any information available about Vesta M. Roy's family?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3281_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3281_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3281_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3281_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3281_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3281_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3281_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3281_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3281_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3281_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3281_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThis answer is derived from the information provided in multiple documents, which consistently state that Vesta M. Roy was born in Dearborn, Michigan."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}